凯尔·辛普森：好的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right,
我们将讨论调用函数的第三种方式使用new关键字。
the third way that we'll look at invoking functions uses the new keyword.
而且我完全理解这个新的关键字似乎有一些
And I fully understand that the new keyword seems as if it has something to
调用类构造函数。
do with invoking class constructors.
这和班级没有任何关系。
This has not got anything to do with classes.
这只是一个不幸的句法
It's just an unfortunate syntactic
让它看起来像是在处理类，而实际上并不是。
trick to make it look like it's dealing with classes when it really isn't.
实际上，new关键字是调用函数的第三种方式。
Actually, the new keyword is the third way that you can invoke a function.
结果是它做了四件非常具体的事情，
And it turns out that it does four very specific things,
我正要为你列出。
which I'm about to list for you.
它做了四件非常具体的事情，
It does four very specific things,
当你看着电话说，这并不是特别明显。
which are not particularly obvious when you look at the call say.
但new关键字的目的实际上是调用
But the purpose of the new keyword is actually to invoke
具有this关键字的函数指向整个新的空对象。
a function with a this keyword pointing at a whole new empty object.
如果我们有调用函数并将它们指向上下文对象，
If we have invoking functions and pointing them at a context object,
就像一个工厂。问吧，这是一种方式。
like a workshop.ask, that's one way.
或者我们说我要调用一个函数，并用.call或给它一个特定的对象
Or we say I'm gonna invoke a function and give it a specific object with .call or
.申请，否则我将用.bind强制它。
.apply or I'm gonna force it with a .bind.
第三种方法是说我想调用一个函数
A third way of doing it is to say I wanna invoke a function and
使用全新的空对象。
use a whole new empty object.
而新的关键字可以实现这一点。
And the new keyword can accomplish that.
它做其他的事情，但它也完成了这个任务，
It does other stuff, but it also accomplishes that task,
这是用一个新的空对象调用一个函数。
which is to invoke a function with a new empty object.
现在，我想说你可以实现同样的目标
Now, I would say that you could accomplish that same goal
通过说，函数点调用，打开，关闭花括号。
by saying, function dot call, open, close curly bracket.
因为它会在一个全新的空对象的上下文中调用您的函数。
Cuz that would invoke your function in the context of a brand new empty object.
所以新的关键字实际上并没有给你买很多东西，除了句法上的糖分，
So the new keyword isn't actually buying you much except the syntactic sugar of,
嘿，我想用一个新的this内容调用这个函数。
hey I want this function invoked with a new this content.
这是我们的第三种也是最后一种方法。
That's our third and final way of doing it.
顺便问一下，这四件事是什么？
So what are those four things by the way?
你会希望能够稍后再参考这张幻灯片。
You're gonna wanna be able to refer back to this slide in a bit.
this关键字的四件事是什么，
What are the four things that the this keyword,
new关键字用于调用我们的函数时将要做的事情，我
that the new keyword is going to do when it's used to invoke our function, what I
用沉重的空气调用引用构造函数调用，这四件事是什么？
call a with heavy air quotes a constructor call, what are those four things?
1号，1号我们创建了一个全新的空对象。
Number 1, number 1 we create a brand new empty object.
嗯，我们已经知道了这一部分，但我们创建了一个全新的空对象
Well we already know that part but we create a brand new empty object out
稀薄的空气，这就是新关键字所做的。
of thin air, that's what the new keyword does.
第二，new关键字将该对象链接到另一个对象。
Number 2, the new keyword links that object to another object.
你在想林克，什么？
And you're thinking link, what?
这就是为什么那里有一个星号。
That's why there's an asterisk there.
我们稍后会回来解释这种联系。
We'll come back and explain the linkage later.
但它首先创建一个全新的对象，然后将其链接到某个地方。
But it first creates a brand new object and then links it somewhere.
然后数字3，它调用函数，
And then number 3, it invokes the function,
它使用其、this、关键字指向新对象来调用函数。
it calls the function with its, this, keyword pointed at the new object.
不是链接对象，而是新对象。
Not the linked object, the new object.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第四个也是最后一个，函数调用后的新关键字是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And fourth and finally, the new keyword after the function call is
完成后，如果该函数没有返回其自己的对象，
done, if that function does not return its own object,
new关键字假设您打算返回此关键字。
the new keyword assumes that you meant to return this keyword.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以每次出现新关键字时都会发生这四件事
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So these four things happen every single time a new keyword is
用函数调用。
invoked with a function.
现在我只想问一个元意义上的问题，
Now I just wanna ask sort of in a meta sense,
哪一个，当我这样描述的时候，
which one, when I describe it this way,
这两个实体中的哪一个看起来像是在做所有的工作？
which of the two entities seems like it's doing all the work?
看起来像是new关键字做了所有的工作，还是
Does it seem like the new keyword is doing all the work, or
看起来像是你的构造函数在做所有的工作吗？
does it seem like your constructor function's doing all the work?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这真的是新的关键字，不是吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's really the new keyword, isn't it?
事实上，如果你把新的功能放在几乎所有的功能前面，
As a matter of fact, if you put new in front of almost any function,
即使是一个完全空的函数，这四种情况都会发生。
even a completely empty function, all four of these things would happen.
就好像这个函数根本不重要。
It’s almost as if the function doesn’t even matter.
新的关键字只是在某种程度上劫持了函数，所以
The new keyword is just sort of hijacking the function so
它可以做这四件事。
that it can do these four things.